I asked, what are your questions
about the side effects of parents?
And for the most part, everybody was like,
trauma, trauma, trauma, trauma.
I have an ex who just is like one of my favorite people
and he has like these quotes and he would always say like,
shame on your parents for what they did back in the day,
but shame on you for staying that way.
Being able to identify like,
oh, I do this because of you and I don't have to.
And that healing is in the empowerment of you saying,
I can take control of my journey.
Next question.
How do you heal from a narcissistic parent,
namely as a daughter with a narcissistic dad?
I think for me, it's been.